Connect with memory.
Man with No Past is a action, drama film directed by James Bamford.
Waking up in an unfamiliar city, a man with no memory must
confront the mysteries of his own identity.
However, his desperate search to uncover the past pits him against a powerful
enemy, leading to a showdown that ultimately reveals the truth.
Sanborn, played by Jon Voight.
Ryder, played by Adam Woodward.
Soach, played by Marton Csokas.
Morgan, played by Charlotte Vega.
Jack, played by Philip Winchester.
Shelly, played by Charlotte Weston.
Back to the Past (Chinese: 尋秦記) is a 2025 Hong Kong historical science fiction action film
directed by Ng Yuen-fai and Jack Lai, with action direction by Sammo Hung.
The film is a continuation of the 2001 television series, A Step into the Past,
which was based on Wong Yee's novel, The Chronicles of Searching Qin.
It stars the original cast members of the series Louis Koo, Raymond Lam, Jessica Hsuan, Sonija
Kwok, Joyce Tang, and Michelle Saram reprising their roles from the series.
Produced by Koo's One Cool Film Production, filming for Back to the Past
began in April 2019 in Guizhou and wrapped up on 7 July 2019.
It was theatrically released on 31 December 2025 in Hong Kong.
The tone is emotional.